

Ndefo Agozilim

UIUX /Graphics Designer

Contact

- +2347061161980
- ndefoago@gmail.com
- No 34A Akinsilure Street, Aguda Surulere

Education

2010 - 2016

BSC, In Computer Science Madonna University Elele

2007 - 2009

WASSCE

Universal Comprehensive School Nsukks

Skills

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Indesign

FIGMA

JAVA SCRIPT

About

Self-disciplined and meticulous User Interface (UI) and User Experience (UX) Designer with 3 years of professional experience. Possesses strong analytical and User-Centeric design skills to create holistic solutions that are functional and research-driven. Produces pixel-perfect visuals and includes usability heuristics into practice. Performs well when multi-task and eager to learn

Work Experience

System Analyst

Present ICT Center ,University Of Nigeria Nsukka

I Worked with different analytics tools to improve the website of the University

IT Sales Support /graphics Designer

2015 - 2016 Nudakol System Onuru estate Lekki phares 1

IT support and worked with graphics tools like photoshop, figma, illustrator and mail chimp for product design which are published in the website

IT Support

2013-2014 System Tech limited, Agunala drive surulere

Responsible for the smooth running of computer systems, routers, switches, internet and ensure users get maximum benefits from them.

Hobbies

- FootballWatching Movies
- Gaming